thedailyneopets.com 2013-12-06

# The Daily Neopets Privacy Policy | The Daily Neopets

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available at the bottom of every page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect**

No personal information will be ever collected without consent from the user. The only place where you will ever be asked to entered personal information is on our contact form and when signing up for a myTDN account. There, you will be asked to fill in your email address and name (other personal information is optional).

**The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when signing up only to register your account in our database. We do not share this information with outside parties.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We will never spam your email with the email addresses we have in our databases. For enhanced security, control, and privacy, you can easily disable email announcements in your account preferences.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that we and certain third parties place in visitors' computer browsers to store their preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

Cookies can only be "read" by their creators. For example, a cookie created by thedailyneopets.com cannot be read by google.com (and the reverse is also true). Therefore, your cookie data is safe and cannot be hacked or tapped by any outside source. Cookies are simply a tool for us to manage the site and give you a better browsing experience.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Your data is safe with us and will not be stolen or sold.

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Other Terms**

We will not be held responsible for the content of off-site links. Visit these websites at your own risk.

**How To Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns, please Contact Us.
